eppicard.com 2019-12-03

# EPPICard - Privacy Policies

PRIVACY POLICIES

Cardholder Privacy Policy

Your privacy and security is important to us. Find your program link below to learn more about how we protect your Privacy.

CONDUENT STATE & LOCAL SOLUTIONS, INC. ONLINE PRIVACY STATEMENT

General

Conduent State & Local Solutions, Inc. ("Conduent") is committed to the privacy and security of personal information you provide to us through the use of Conduent websites. This Online Privacy Statement ("Statement") informs you of the information practices for Conduent websites, including the type of personal information we collect from your use of Conduent websites, how the information is used, and with whom the information is shared.

By using our site, you agree that your use is subject to the terms of this Statement and you consent to the collection, use and storage of your information by Conduent in accordance with this Statement and as may be more specifically explained on each site. Conduent may change this Statement at any time and will display the changes here on this site. Because your use of this site after changes have been posted indicates your agreement with those changes, we encourage you to visit this Statement on a regular basis. If you are not comfortable with using this site in accordance with this Statement, please exit the site immediately.

You may have accessed this site as a result of a link from another Conduent site. This Statement applies to all Conduent sites linked to this site except where more specific information is provided on the linked site with respect to the collection, use and storage of personal information.

Collection and Use of Information

You may visit this site and certain other Conduent sites without registering or disclosing personally identifiable information, although some areas of this site or other sites may require a password. Conduent may ask you to provide personal information, such as when you are asked to complete an online form or a request with regard to a product or service from Conduent. This information may include name, physical address, phone number, email address and other personal information that you choose to provide. Conduent uses this information for purposes of communications with you, to respond to requests you may have, and for marketing purposes. If you wish to update information you provided through this site in connection with regular mailings or you wish to have your name removed from a mailing list, you may do so by sending an email or by submitting an updated form through the same communication channel you initially submitted the information.

Certain Conduent sites allow for the electronic submission of resumes if you are interested in employment opportunities with Conduent. Resumes received by Conduent are used only for employment purposes or such other purpose you may request. If you wish to delete or update employment-related information you submitted through this site, you may do so by using the profile management function that is available or contact Conduent Human Resources.

When you visit this Site, we may automatically collect certain information relating to you, such as your Internet Protocol (IP) address of the device you use to connect to the Internet, Internet service provider, type of operating system, the time and date you accessed the site. Also, when you visit our site we may collect information through the use of "cookies". A cookie is a small file that a website can send to your browser and then is stored on your computer. This type of technology is designed to tell us when you reenter our site, pages you viewed while on our site, and the type of browser you use. You can control whether to accept any cookies or not. Although if you decide not to accept cookies, some features on our site may not work properly without the use of cookies. If you prefer not to accept cookies you can change the settings in your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, which lets you choose whether or not to accept it. The information collected helps us identify data relating to usage and trends, address any problems with site administration, and to further improve this site.

Mobile Application

For you convenience, Conduent offers you the ability to access some of our products and services on your mobile device. When accepting mobile agreement we may collect information from your individual devices such as phone number, device type, IP address, information about your location or other device settings. We use this information to ensure application is functioning properly and to help us understand how the mobile application is being used. Information we collect will not be shared with any third-party service providers.

Sharing of Information with Third Parties

Conduent will not sell or give your personal information to third parties for their use for purposes unrelated to Conduent without your permission.

Conduent may share personal information about you with our subsidiaries and affiliated companies. We also may share personal information with our suppliers, contractors and agents who perform functions on our behalf, or in connection with products and services offered by Conduent or a request made by you. Conduent may disclose your personal information as we consider necessary to comply with the law or governmental authorities, in connection with litigation, dispute resolution, or administration of this Statement or a possible violation of this site's Terms of Use or the rights of Conduent or a third party. In addition, Conduent may disclose or receive personal information in connection with a possible sale, purchase, merger or other reorganization of a business.

Retention

Conduent will retain personal information collected by a site for as long as it is needed to fulfill the purpose for which the information was provided, to maintain a record of communications with you, or as required by applicable law.

Security

To protect the personal information we receive Conduent uses certain security measures designed to guard against the loss, misuse and alteration of that information. It should be recognized, however, that we cannot guarantee that transmission of data over the Internet will be absolutely secure. Due to the open nature of the Internet the information you provide may be in environments that do not have adequate security measures and may be accessed and used by persons other than those intended. As a result, while protection of your personal information is important to us, Conduent is not able to ensure the security of information you transmit to us and you assume the risk of any third party obtaining that information. Upon receipt of your information Conduent will strive to ensure its security on our systems.

Links to Other Web Sites

This site may contain links to other websites, not maintained by Conduent. If you choose to access those sites, please review the Privacy Statement applicable to each site. The links to other sites are made available as a convenience to you and Conduent is not responsible for the privacy policies and information collection practices of those sites.

Conduent Client Websites

In the course of providing services to its clients, Conduent may operate websites for certain clients that involve the collection, use and retention of personal information. For example, if you are a health plan member, health plan provider, a patient or other individual who does business with an Conduent client, Conduent may collect, use and maintain personal information in order to provide you with services on behalf of the client. Those activities are conducted by Conduent under a contract between Conduent and the client. This Statement is not intended to modify the terms of the contract between Conduent and the client. If you have questions about the handling of your personal information that are not addressed on the specific website through which Conduent conducts those activities on behalf of the client, please use the contact information listed on that site or communicate with the Conduent client.

Global Presence

Conduent has employees, customers and suppliers in many countries around the world. The management, operational and technical processes and systems used by Conduent may involve transfer of information across borders. For example, personal information you give to Conduent may be sent to systems outside the country in which you initially provided the information, and it may be processed and stored in a different country. Regardless of where you provide your personal information, Conduent will take steps to handle it in a secure manner in accordance with this Statement and all applicable laws.

Children

Conduent does not market its products or services to children under thirteen years of age. We do not intend to collect personal information from children and request that children do not submit personal information to us.

Scope of Statement

This Statement describes the online privacy practices for Conduent Websites maintained by Conduent State & Local Solutions, Inc. ("Conduent"). It does not modify any agreements Conduent may have with our customers, suppliers or other third parties.

Contact Information

Please call the number on the back of your Card with any questions you might have about this Statement. 

This Online Privacy Statement was last modified March 23, 2017
